Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Staff Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Courant, Paul and Marilyn Knepp
  - Schools, Colleges and Units Budget Files
    - Fiscal Year 2002
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 447)
        - General, 2001 (Box 447)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - General, 2001 (Box 447)
      - Auxiliary Units Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 447)
      - Bentley Library
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 447)
        - General, 2000 (Box 447)
          [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2033 ]
      - Business Administration
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 447)
      - Center for the Education of Women (CEW)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - General, 2001 (Box 447)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
      - Clements Library Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
      - Dearborn
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - General, 2000 (Box 447)
      - Dentistry, School of (Dental)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
      - Education, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 447)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 447)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 448)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
      - Evaluations and Examinations, Office of -- Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
      - Executive Vice President (EVP) for Academic Affairs Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
      - Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (EVPCFO)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 448)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - General, 2000 (Box 448)
      - Flint Budget Planning, 2001 (Box 448)
      - Financial Aid Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
      - General Counsel Commitments, 2000 (Box 448)
      - Health Services
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
      - Hospitals
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 448)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action (HRAA) Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 448)
      - Information, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 448)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 448)
        - General, 2001 (Box 448)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 448)
        - Commitments, 1999-2001 (Box 448)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - Rate Change, 2000-2001; 5 folders (Box 448)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 448)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 448)
        - General, 1998-2000 (Box 449)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
      - International Institute Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
      - Kinesiology, Division of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
      - Law School
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
        - General, 2000 (Box 449)
      - Life Sciences Institute
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 449)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 4 folders (Box 449)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Services (MAIS)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
        - General, 2001 (Box 449)
      - Media Union
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 449)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 449)
        - General, 2000 (Box 449)
      - Medical School
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 449)
        - Commitments, 1999-2000 (Box 449)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 449)
      - MERIT (Box 450)
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 450)
      - Museum of Art
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - General, 2000 (Box 450)
      - Music, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - General, 2000 (Box 450)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - General, 2000 (Box 450)
      - Nichols Arboretum
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 450)
      - Nursing, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 450)
      - Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives (OAMI) Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
      - Office of Budget and Planning Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
      - Officer Education Program
        - Air Force Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Army Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Navy
          - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
          - Commitments, 2001 (Box 450)
      - Office of New Student Programs Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research
        - ADVANCE, 2001 (Box 450)
        - Cost Sharing, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Life Sciences Corridor, 2001 (Box 450)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
      - President Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
      - Public Health, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - General, 2000 (Box 450)
      - Public Policy, Gerald R. Ford School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - General, ca. 2000 (Box 450)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 450)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
      - Recreational Sports
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 2001 (Box 451)
      - Registrar, Office of Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
      - Research Units Budget Planning, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 451)
      - General, 2001 (Box 451)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA)
        - Budget Planning, 1999-2001 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 451)
      - Social Work, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 451)
      - Student Publications Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
      - Undergraduate Admissions
        - Budget Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 451)
        - General, 2001 (Box 451)
      - University Library
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 1998-2000 (Box 451)
      - Vice President (VP) Communications
        - Commitments, 2000 (Box 451)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
      - Vice President (VP) Development
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 2001 (Box 451)
      - Vice President (VP) for Government Relations
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
      - Vice President of Research
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
      - Vice President (VP) and Secretary of the University
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 451)
        - General, undated (Box 451)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2034 ]
      - Vice President (VP) for Student Affairs
        - Budget Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 451)
    - Fiscal Year 2003
      - ADVANCE Commitments, 2002 (Box 451)
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, Taubman College of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 451)
        - General, 2002 (Box 451)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 451)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 451)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 451)
      - Auxiliary Units Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 451)
      - Bentley Historical Library (Box 452)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 452)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - Center for the Education of Women (CEW)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Clements Library
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 452)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2023 ]
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2002 (Box 452)
      - Dearborn
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Education, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - Engineering, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - Evaluations and Examinations, Office of, Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (EVP and CFO)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 1998-2002 (Box 452)
      - Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs (EVPMA) Commitments, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Financial Aid
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2002 (Box 452)
      - Flint, 2001 (Box 452)
      - General Counsel
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Health Services
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Hospitals
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Human Resources
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Information, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 452)
      - Institute for Social Research
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - International Institute
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001 (Box 452)
      - Information Technology Central Services (ITCS)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2002 (Box 452)
      - IT COM
        - Budget Planning, 2000 (Box 452)
        - Budget Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 452)
      - Kinesiology, Division of (Box 453)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 453)
        - General, 2001 (Box 453)
      - Law School Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
      - Life Sciences Institute
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - Courses, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
      - Life Sciences Values and Society Project (LSVSP)
        - Budget Planning, 2001 (Box 453)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 453)
        - General, 2000 (Box 453)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 5 folders (Box 453)
        - Budget Resources, 2001 (Box 453)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Services (MAIS)
        - Background Material, 1999-2000 (Box 453)
        - Budget Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 453)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
      - Media Union
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 453)
        - Media Union Reorganization, 2000 (Box 453)
      - Medical School
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001 (Box 454)
      - MERIT Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Miscellaneous Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Music, Theatre, and Dance, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001 (Box 454)
      - Museum of Art
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001 (Box 454)
        - General Counsel, 2001 (Box 548)
          [Patient/client records restricted until July 01, 2101 ]
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 454)
        - General, 2002 (Box 454)
      - New Student Programs Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Nichols Arboretum
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2000-2002 (Box 454)
      - Nursing, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001 (Box 454)
      - Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives (OAMI)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research (OVPR)
        - Ford Nuclear Reactor, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - MPrime, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Officer Education
        - Air Force Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Army
          - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
          - Commitments, 2001 (Box 454)
        - Navy Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 454)
      - President
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001 (Box 454)
      - Public Health, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Public Policy, Gerald R. Ford School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Ford School Ph.D., 2000 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001 (Box 454)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2000-2002 (Box 454)
      - Recreational Sports
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2002 (Box 454)
      - Registrar, Office of, Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA)
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Social Work, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
      - Student Publications Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
      - Undergraduate Admissions
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 454)
      - University Library
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 454)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 454)
        - General, 2002 (Box 455)
      - University Musical Society Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
      - Vice President for Communications
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 455)
      - Vice President for Development
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 455)
      - Vice for Government Relations
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 455)
        - General, 2000-2001 (Box 455)
      - Vice President for Research
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - General, 2000-2002 (Box 455)
      - Vice President and Secretary of the University
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 455)
      - Vice President for Student Affairs
        - Budget Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2001 (Box 455)
        - Cost Sharing, 2001-2002 (Box 455)
    - Fiscal Year 2004
      - Admissions
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 455)
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, Taubman College of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
      - Art and Design, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 455)
        - General, 2002 (Box 455)
      - Auxiliary Units Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
      - Bentley Historical Library
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 455)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - General, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
      - Center for the Education of Women (CEW) Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
      - Clements Library
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 455)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 455)
      - Dearborn Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 455)
        - General, 2003 (Box 455)
      - Education, School of (Box 456)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - General, 2004 (Box 456)
          [Executive records restricted until July 01, 2024 ]
      - Engineering, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
        - General, 2003 (Box 456)
      - Evaluations and Examinations, Office of, Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
      - Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (EVP and CFO)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Financial Aid
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
      - General Counsel
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
        - General, 2001-2003 (Box 456)
      - Health Services Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
      - Hospitals Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action (HRAA)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 456)
        - General, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Information, School of
        - Budget and Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 456)
      - Information Technology Central Services (ITCS)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
        - General, 2003 (Box 456)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
      - International Institute
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 456)
        - General, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Kinesiology, Division of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 456)
        - General, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Law School
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 456)
        - General, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Life Sciences Institute
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Life Sciences Values and Society Project (LSVSP) Budget Planning, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - General, 2002 (Box 456)
      - Media Union Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
      - Medical School
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 456)
      - MERIT Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Services (MAIS)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - General, 2003 (Box 457)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Music, Theatre, and Dance, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Museum of Art
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2003 (Box 457)
      - Nichols Arboretum
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
      - Nursing, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives (OAMI)
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Office of Budget and Planning Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
      - Officer Education
        - Air Force Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Army Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Navy Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
      - Office of New Student Programs
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002 (Box 457)
      - President
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Public Health, School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2003-2004 (Box 457)
      - Public Policy, Gerald R. Ford School of
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Rackham Graduate School
        - Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
        - Commitments, 2002-2004 (Box 457)
        - General, 2002 (Box 457)
      - Recreational Sports Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)
      - Registrar, Office of, Budget Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 457)